Hi, and that's lesson I will do a quick overview of what his hip hop hop pilot is.
If hop hop pilot is an AI-powered coding assistant integrated into Visual Studio Code.
You of course can use it also with different IDs like JetBrains or others.
So hip hop hop pilot was created to help you write your code faster and with less effort.
It also allows you to focus more energy on problem solving and collaboration.
It was training on public repositories and can assist you with most programming languages
and frameworks.
It has a full support of Python development with intelligent code completion.
It also can assist you with JavaScript and all-related JavaScript frameworks like React,
Node.js, Swital and others. It also supports many other languages like Java, C#, Ruby,
Goal and others. So be honest, it supports almost all programming languages already popular
so you can use it with whatever you want.
Now let's talk about the pilot features which was created to enhance your coding experience
and productivity.
So with it hop hop pilot you can get call suggestions as you type in your ID.
So it means when you start typing your code it will show you some suggestions which should
be relevant for what you want to do.
It tried to predict on your actions on your file context.
So what you want to do and suggest you some code which you can just apply and save your
time when you type in it.
You can also use chat with your pilot to ask for some help with your code.
You just open chat interface, write a question, it answers you, it also can show some
code fragments, support suggestions, directly in the chat interface and you can just easily
apply it or decline it.
You can also ask a pilot using some common line if it's more common way to work with
AI assistance to you.
You can also organize and share task specific context to get more relevant answers.
What it means, it means when you for example work in main application files, file and you
want to write some functionality which related to other files you can also add to the
context, the rest of the files and hit hop will provide you more relevant answers because
it will know the which files it might affect.
You can also generate description of the changes in pull requests but it's only a pilot
enterprise.
Plan available.
You can also create managed collections of documents, with the code knowledge basis as
it has a better context but it's only for enterprise plan.
You can also work on code suggestions and create pull requests for your review.
So, but it's available in the pilot pro and the pilot enterprise only plans.
ACC is really a really has a big number of features which can help and without the development
process.
In one of the next lessons, I will do a overview of payment plans and you can decide
what payment plans plan is more suitable for you.
So, let's not talk where a private is available.
Right of course available in your ID or quality data like Visual Studio Code, JetBrains,
some others.
You can use it in your hop mobile for some charter systems.
You can use it in Windows Terminal, Canary through the terminal chart interface, a post
in comment line if you use GitHub CLI or you can use it even on GitHub website.
For example, when you do some closed review just searching your code and others.
So, as you see, it's available across multiple platforms so you can support your development
workflow whenever you are.
Now let's talk and let's see how it happens to look like.
I visited the website of the hopcop pilot.
You can find this link in the resources for this lesson and I will show you a quick video
how it works so you have a chart interface from the right side where you type your message.
You can also choose the mode and choose the mode you want to use and it makes some suggestions
to you and you can easily apply it or decline it so it changes the code in the files depending
on suggestions.
So, but more precise over you of all the interface of Visuals, you can use you to see in the
next sections.
So, I hope it was really useful to you and now you better understand what the pilot is
and see you in the next lessons.